Antonios Koukouves

Berlin, Kaiserdamm 116, Germany 14057 (+30)6955852635 | antonis.kkvs@gmail.com

Professional with expertise in programming, cybersecurity, and cloud technologies. I've successfully applied Siemens technologies to Fujitsu's cloud heat pumps, boosting sales and after-sales services. I've also provided remote control solutions for specialized air conditioning systems in pharmaceutical warehouses, the Tositsa Foundation, and the Acropolis Museum. Currently holding a Cybersecurity certification from the University of Patras and am actively pursuing further certifications in cloud and DevOps technologies.

Websites, Portfolios, Profiles

www.linkedin.com/in/antonis-koukouves-6b6151261

Work History

Technical Support Engineer

Fujitsu General South-East Europe, Athens, Attiki January 2023 - Current

- Working in After-Sales at Fujitsu, specializing in providing solutions for centralized control of air conditioning systems through cloud-based and centralized computer control
- Binging expertise in computers, cybersecurity, and administration, with deep knowledge of Fujitsu technologies and tools.

Cyber Security Specialist

Freelance/Self Employed, Athens, Attiki

February 2022 - Current

- I engage in daily practice and study new techniques in bug bounty hunting and penetration testing
- I write code while learning programming languages such as Python and JavaScript
- As I transition career, I am self-taught and actively pursuing certifications in AWS Cloud, Azure Cloud Administration, DevOps, Bug Bounty Hunting, and Penetration Testing
- I also hold certification in Cybersecurity from University of Patras.

Service Manager/Technician

FG Europe S.A, Glyfada, Attiki

January 2020 - January 2023

 Promoted to Workshop Manager at Midea Greece's headquarters, where I provided technical support for IoT solutions to engineers working with major companies, industries, and institutions.

Technical Support Engineer

FG Europe S.A, Glyfada, Attiki

March 2017 - January 2020

- Advancing to a Professional Air Conditioning Technician specializing in large-scale central air conditioning systems
- I also worked with networks and computers in this field.

Practicum Student

FG Europe S.A, Glyfada, Attiki

August 2016 - February 2017

• During my internship, I served as an Assistant Air Conditioning Technician.

Education

HVAC Technician June 2016

IEK AKMH, Athens, Attiki

Vocational School June 2013

Elliniko, Elliniko, Attiki

Skills

- Computer literacy
- Communication skills
- English
- Customer service
- Linux-Apache-MySQL-PHP Stack
- Critical Thinking
- Fast-learner
- Coding
- Problem-Solving
- Teamwork and Collaboration
- Bug tracking

Languages

Greek		
English	German	

Hobbies

My hobbies include studying, coding, crafting ethical hacking tools, and working on Raspberry Pi projects. I'm passionate about technology and machine learning, running my own AI models locally on my home-server based on psychology, penetration testing, and coding using Ollama. I also read books and practicing on different technology fields using Udemy and other internet sources.

Volunteering

Served in the Greek Special Forces as a Commando - Paratrooper $\,$